<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Systems/Solutions on User9 Docs n Recs</title>
    <link>https://ice-energy.github.io/user9/categories/systems/solutions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Systems/Solutions on User9 Docs n Recs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2008 - 2018, Ice-Energy; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 12:19:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ice-energy.github.io/user9/categories/systems/solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Github Plus Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ice-energy.github.io/user9/post/post_009/githubhugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 12:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ice-energy.github.io/user9/post/post_009/githubhugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is an open-source static website generator. It has many themes and many layouts ready to choose from. Content in Hugo consists of posts that you add using markdown format, and the posts are arranged in a logical directory tree structure. See the Hugo site here: Hugo Website.
I put together 3 Hugo sites, using the same set of post files. Have a quick look:
 ice-energy.github.io/jreed ice-energy.github.io/user1 ice-energy.github.io/user9  3 questions you probably have after looking at that:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wall-Mounted Desktop</title>
      <link>https://ice-energy.github.io/user9/post/post_008/wallmounted_desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 12:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ice-energy.github.io/user9/post/post_008/wallmounted_desktop/</guid>
      <description>Because every Mad (Computer) Scientist needs their Hardware Wall-Mounted!
I put together this computer largely from spare parts and Amazon points from my Amex. So barely cost anything, and I thought it would be perfect as a server for Zoneminder.
This was built with the intention of putting it in an enclosure. It started out sitting on my bookshelf, where I used some half-inch standoffs to raise it up. Here&amp;rsquo;s a pic:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IceBear Control Using PLC</title>
      <link>https://ice-energy.github.io/user9/post/post_007/plc_controls_icebear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 14:55:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ice-energy.github.io/user9/post/post_007/plc_controls_icebear/</guid>
      <description>Quick Summary: An off-the-shelf external controller may be used to interface directly with the CDC controller to control the IceBears&amp;rsquo; cycle of Making Ice and Providing Cooling. An example scenario will be shown using a PLC-type controller with a Modbus interface that is used to control an IceBear AND ALSO extract data from it.
CDC Controller GPIO Inputs:   The CDC controller has 8 GPIO inputs as shown in the above picture:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>